Let me introduce someone
This is the technician
I hired at great expense
A university graduate too
Zane
Here's your 200,000 bonus
Thank you, Mr. Daniel
The previous farming methods was too crude
Not professional at all
I plan to increase stocking density
and cut feed costs
We can boost profits
by two to three times
Good
As expected of a college grad
You really get what you pay for
If you can really do it
I'll double your bonus then
Increase density
Cut feed costs
If they keep this up
these frogs won't survive
In two months
skin rot will explode
Lewes
Why did you stand up
Don't tell me
you think I meant you
Did he seriously think
it was him
A high school grad
compared to a university guy
Doesn't he know his place
Would Daniel take him seriously
Daniel
Do you have any conscience
Lewes worked for you
for two years, killing himself
Let alone a bonus
you didn't even pay him a cent
He only just joined
And you gave him 200,000
Who are you looking down on
You still dare say that
Can Lewes compare to a college grad
Cynthia
Your dad is right
Look at the man you married
He can't even speak properly
and assist Daniel properly
And he thinks he deserves credit
Sandra
Your words are too harsh
Too harsh
Your Lewes is useless
He deserves it
Since you think I'm a disgrace
we'll leave
Lewes
Uncle, Auntie, don't get mad
My parents are just worried
He doesn't know anything
Seeing me making money
he insisted on taking the 50,000 I gave him
and got himself deep in debt
to raise forest frogs like me
Isn't that ridiculous
You good-for-nothing
With your brain
you can't even help Daniel
And you still want to farm frogs
Now you're drowning in debt
Are you trying to ruin my daughter